Guide to the Vassar College Drama Department Records, circa 1910-2021
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series III. Experimental Theatre Visual Materials, 1925-1979
  - Photographs, 1925-1979
    - Come Out into the Sun, 1935 Aug (Folder 13.6)
    - Lady from the Sea, 1935 Dec (Folder 13.7)
    - Lady from the Sea, 1935 Dec (Folder 14.1)
    - Lady from the Sea, 1935 Dec (Map Case - F4)
    - Summer Session, The Dance of Death, 1935 (Folder 69.13)
    - Question Before the House, 1935 Mar (Folder 69.14)
    - My Country Right or Left, 1935 May (Folder 69.15)
    - The Lady from the Sea, 1935 Dec (Folder 69.16)
    - How Are Ye Blind, 1936 Feb (Folder 69.17)
    - How Are Ye Blind!, 1936 Feb (Folder 14.2)
    - Fuente Ovejuna, 1936 May (Folder 14.3)
    - Fuente Ovejuna, 1936 May (Folder 69.18)
    - Fuente Ovejuna, 1936 May (Map Case - F4)
    - Tonight We Improvise, 1936 Dec (Folders 14.4-14.5)
    - Tonight We Improvise, 1936 Dec (Folder 69.19)
    - Tonight We Improvise, 1936 Dec (Map Case - F5)
    - Backgrounds of the Modern Theatre, 1937 Jan (Folder 14.6)
    - Backgrounds of the Modern Theatre, 1937 Jan (Folder 69.20)
    - Backgrounds of the Modern Theatre, 1937 Jan (Map Case - F5)
    - No More Peace, 1937 Feb (Folders 14.7-14.8)
    - No More Peace, 1937 Feb (Folder 15.1)
    - No More Peace, 1937 Feb (Map Case - F5)
    - No More Peace, 1937 Feb (Folder 69.21)
    - Relax!, 1937 Apr (Folder 15.2)
    - Relax!, 1937 Apr (Map Case - F5)
    - Fallen Mangoes, 1937 Apr (Folders 15.3-15.4)
    - Fallen Mangoes, 1937 Apr (Folder 69.22)
    - Fallen Mangoes, 1937 Apr (Map Case - F5)
    - Relax, 1937 Apr (Folder 69.22)
    - One-Third of a Nation, 1937 Jul (Folder 15.5)
    - The Infernal Machine, 1937 Dec (Folder 15.6)
    - The Infernal Machine, 1937 Dec (Folder 69.23)
    - The Infernal Machine, 1937 Dec (Map Case - F6)
    - Knight of the Burning Pestle, 1938 Feb (Folders 15.7-15.8)
    - Knight of the Burning Pestle, 1938 Feb (Folder 4.1)
    - Knight of the Burning Pestle, 1938 Feb (Map Case - F6)
    - I Have Seen Myself Before, 1938 Apr (Folder 4.2)
    - Three Plays on American Homelife, 1938 Apr (Folder 16.1)
    - Three Plays on American Homelife, 1938 Apr (Folder 69.24)
    - Three Plays on American Homelife, 1938 Apr (Map Case - F6)
    - Vassar's Folly, 1938 Dec or 1940 Jun (Folders 16.2-16.5)
    - Vassar's Folly, 1938 (Folder 4.3)
    - Vassar's Folly, 1938-1939 (Map Case - F7)
    - Peter Goes to the Fair, 1939 Feb (Folders 16.6-16.7)
    - Peter Goes to the Fair, 1939 Feb (Folder 4.4)
    - Peter Goes to the Fair, 1939 Feb (Folder 69.26)
    - Peter Goes to the Fair, 1939 Feb (Map Case - F7)
    - The Three Sisters, 1939 Apr (Folder 16.8)
    - The Three Sisters, 1939 Apr (Folder 4.5)
    - The Three Sisters, 1939 Apr (Folder 69.26)
    - The Three Sisters, 1939 Apr (Map Case - F7)
    - Orpheus, 1939 Dec (Folder 16.9)
    - Orpheus, 1939 Dec (Folder 4.6)
    - Orpheus, 1939 Dec (Folder 69.27)
    - Orpheus, 1939 Dec (Map Case - F7)
    - Escape or No Escape (Includes "Escape for Jane," "Check for Eight Dollars," "Prelude," and "Mr. Sycamore"), 1940 Feb (Folder 17.1)
    - Escape or No Escape, 1940 Feb (Folder 5.1)
    - Escape or No Escape, 1940 Feb (Folder 70.1)
    - Escape or No Escape, 1940 Feb (Map Case - F7)
    - Our Town, 1940 Dec (Folders 17.2-17.3)
    - Our Town, 1940 Dec (Folder 70.2)
    - Pillars of Society, 1941 Feb (Folder 70.3)
    - Pillars of Society, 1941 Feb (Folder 17.4)
    - Pillars of Society, 1941 Feb (Map Case - F8)
    - Sight Unseen, 1941 Apr (Folders 17.5-17.7)
    - Sight Unseen, 1941 Apr (Map Case - F10)
    - Sight Unseen, 1941 Apr (Folder 70.4)
    - Murder in the Cathedral, 1941 Dec (Folder 70.5)
    - Murder in the Cathedral, 1941 Dec (Folder 17.8)
    - Murder in the Cathedral, 1941 Dec (Folder 18.1)
    - Murder in the Cathedral, 1941 Dec (Map Case - F10)
    - Santos Vega, 1942 Feb (Folder 70.6)
    - Santos Vega, 1942 (Folder 18.4)
    - Phoenix, 1942 Apr (Folder 18.2)
    - Phoenix, 1942 Apr (Map Case - F8)
    - War Chest Rally, 1942 Nov (Folder 18.3)
    - War Chest Rally, 1942 Nov (Map Case - F8)
    - War Chest Rally, 1942 Nov (Folder 70.7)
    - St. Joan, 1942-1943 (Folder 22.4)
    - St. Joan, 1942-1943 (Map Case - F10)
    - Saint Joan, 1943 Apr (Folder 70.9)
    - Elmer and Lily, 1943 May (Folder 70.10)
    - Elmer and Lily, 1942-1943 (Folder 18.5)
    - Elmer and Lily, 1942-1943 (Map Case - F10)
    - St. Joan, 1942-1943 (Folders 18.6-18.7)
    - Medea, 1943 (Folder 70.8)
    - Peer Gynt, 1946 Mar (Folder 5.2)
    - She Would be a Soldier, 1943 Dec (Folder 18.8)
    - She Would be a Soldier, 1943 Dec (Folder 70.11)
    - The Tempest, 1944 Mar (Folders 70.12 – 70.13)
    - The Tempest, 1944 Mar (Folder 18.9)
    - Him, 1944 Dec (Folders 70.14 – 70.15)
    - Sunny Morning, 1945 Mar (Folder 71.1)
    - No Strings Attached, 1945 Mar (Folder 71.1)
    - Twelve Pound Look, 1945 Mar (Folder 71.1)
    - Trifles, 1945 Mar (Folder 71.1)
    - Theatre of the Soul, 1945 Mar (Folder 71.1)
    - Bodas de Sangre, Blood Wedding, 1945 Jun (Folder 71.2)
    - Back to Methuselah, 1946 Nov (Folder 71.3)
    - Back to Methuselah, 1946 (Folder 19.1)
    - Les Mouches, 1947 Apr (Folder 9.2)
    - Les Mouches, 1947 Apr (Folders 22.5-22.7 (Oversize))
    - Les Mouches, 1947 Apr (Folder 71.4)
    - Tobias and the Angel, 1947 Dec (Folder 71.5)
    - Tobias and the Angel, 1947-1948 (Map Case - F9)
    - The Learned Ladies, 1948 Mar (Folder 71.6)
    - The Spook Sonata, 1948 Apr (Folder 71.7)
    - The Alcestis of Euripides, 1948 Dec (Folder 71.8)
    - The Provok’d Wife, 1949 Mar (Folder 71.9)
    - The Good Woman of Setzuan [The Good Person of Szechwan], 1949 Apr (Folder 71.10)
    - From Morn to Midnight, 1949 Dec (Folder 71.11)
    - Electre, 1950 Mar (Folder 71.12)
    - Electre, 1949-1950 (Folder 19.3)
    - Electre, 1949-1950 (Folders 23.1-23.3 (Oversize))
    - The Trojan Women, 1950-1951 (Map Case - F9)
    - The Trojan Women, 1950 Dec (Folder 71.13)
    - Hedda Gabler, 1950-1951 (Folder 19.4)
    - The Gardener’s Dog, 1951 Feb (Folder 71.14)
    - Finnegan's Wake, 1951 May (Folder 19.5)
    - Finnegan's Wake, 1951 May (Folder 24.1 (Oversize))
    - Orpheus, 1951 May (Folder 71.15)
    - Finnegan's Wake, 1951 Dec (Folder 72.1)
    - Orpheus, 1951 (Folder 24.2 (Oversize))
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1952 Mar (Folder 72.2)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1952 (Folder 19.6)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1952 (Folder 24.3 (Oversize))
    - Farfetched Fables, 1952 Dec (Folder 72.3)
    - The Shewing-up of Blanco Posnet, 1952 Dec (Folder 72.3)
    - Madwoman of Chaillot, 1952 (Folder 24.4 (Oversize))
    - The Critic, 1953 Mar (Folder 72.4)
    - Right You Are, 1953 May (Folder 72.5)
    - Lysistrata, 1953 Dec (Folder 72.6)
    - Mother of Us All, 1954 Mar (Folder 72.7)
    - The Crucible, 1954 (Folder 19.7)
    - The Crucible, 1954 (Folder 24.5 (Oversize))
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 1955 (Folder 19.8)
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 1955 Mar (Folder 73.1)
    - Ondine, 1955 May (Folder 73.2)
    - Ondine, 1955 (Folder 19.10)
    - Ondine, 1955 (Folder 24.6 (Oversize))
    - Heartbreak House, 1955 (Folder 19.9)
    - Heartbreak House, 1955 Nov (Folder 73.3)
    - The Alchemist, 1956 Mar (Folder 25.1 (Oversize))
    - The Alchemist, 1956 Mar (Folder 73.4)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1956 May (Folder 73.5)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1956 May (Folder 19.11)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1956 May (Folder 25.2 (Oversize))
    - Three Sisters, 1956 Dec (Folder 19.12)
    - Three Sisters, 1956 Dec (Folder 25.3 (Oversize))
    - Three Sisters, 1956 Dec (Folder 73.6)
    - Noah, 1957 Mar (Folder 73.8)
    - Noah, 1957 (Folder 19.14)
    - Him, 1957 May (Folder 73.9)
    - A Winter’s Tale, 1957 Dec (Folder 73.10)
    - A Winter’s Tale, 1957 (Folder 19.13)
    - A Winter’s Tale, 1957 (Folder 25.4 (Oversize))
    - Everyman, 1957 (Folder 73.7)
    - Disdain, circa 1957 (Folder 25.5 (Oversize))
    - To Damascus, 1958 Mar (Folder 73.11)
    - To Damascus, 1958 (Folder 19.16)
    - Franz Kafka's Amerika, 1958 May (Folder 19.15)
    - The Lesson, 1958 Dec (Folder 73.12)
    - The Bald Soprano, 1958 Dec (Folder 73.12)
    - The Masque of Comus, 1959 Mar (Folder 19.17)
    - The Masque of Comus, 1959 Mar (Folder 73.13)
    - Unidentified productions, circa 1955-1958 (Folders 25.6-25.7 (Oversize))
    - Unidentified production with Spanish setting, circa 1950s (Folders 21.1-21.3)
    - Ring Around the Moon, 1959 May (Folder 73.14)
    - Mary Stuart, Don Carlos, Maid of Orleans, 1959 Nov (Folder 73.15)
    - Arms and the Man, 1959 Dec (Folder 73.16)
    - Standing Room Only, 1960 Mar (Folder 74.1)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot, 1960 May (Folder 74.2)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot, 1960 May (Folder 74.4)
    - The Madwoman of Chaillot, 1960 May (Folder 19.18)
    - The Cherry Orchard, 1960 (Folder 19.19)
    - The Cherry Orchard, 1960 Dec (Folders 74.3-7.4)
    - A Doll's House, 1961 (Folder 19.20)
    - A Doll's House, 1961 Mar (Folders 74.4-7.5)
    - The Matchmaker, 1961 Dec (Folder 74.6)
    - The Matchmaker, 1961 (Folder 19.21)
    - The Trojan War Will Not Take Place, 1962 Mar (Folder 19.22)
    - Crimes and Crimes, 1962 (Folder 19.23)
    - Hansel and Gretel, 1963 Mar (Folder 74.7)
    - Skin of Our Teeth, 1963 May (Folder 74.8)
    - Smiles of a Summer Night, 1963 Oct 31 (Folder 74.9)
    - Smiles of a Summer Night (negatives), 1963 Oct 31 (Box 95)
    - The Trojan Women, 1963 Dec (Folder 19.24)
    - The Trojan Women, 1963 Dec (Folder 74.10)
    - The Triumph of Honor, 1964 Feb (Folder 74.11)
    - Pericles, Prince of Tyre, 1964 Mar (Folder 74.12)
    - A Shakespeare Celebration, 1964 Apr (Folder 75.1)
    - Spreading the News, 1964 Apr (Folder 75.2)
    - Suddenly Last Summer, 1964 Apr (Folder 75.3)
    - Ugly Duckling, 1964 Apr (Folder 75.4)
    - Aria De Capo, 1964 Apr (Folder 75.5)
    - Land of Hearts Desire, 1964 Apr (Folder 75.6)
    - Boy With A Cart, 1964 Apr (Folder 75.7)
    - The Sandbox, 1964 Oct (Folder 75.8)
    - Don Juan in Hell, 1964 Oct (Folder 19.25)
    - The Lacquer Box, 1964 Nov (Folder 75.9)
    - Uncle Vanya, 1964 Dec (Folder 75.10)
    - Second Shepard's Play, 1964 (Folder 19.26)
    - The Amorous Brother, 1965 Feb (Folder 76.1)
    - The Italian Straw Hat, 1965 Mar (Folder 76.2)
    - The Hour Glass, Overtones, Hello from Bertha, 1965 Mar (Folder 76.3)
    - The Purification, Excerpts from Camino Real, 1965 May (Folder 76.4)
    - Electra, 1965 Oct (Folder 76.5)
    - Toad of Toad Hall, 1965 Nov (Folder 76.6)
    - A Month in the Country, 1965 Dec (Folder 76.7)
    - What a Wonder is Woman, 1965 (Folder 19.27)
    - Camino Real, 1965 (Folder 19.28)
    - Maid of the Mill, 1966 Feb (Folder 19.29)
    - Maid of the Mill, 1966 Feb (Folder 76.8)
    - A Question of Confidence, 1966 Mar (Folder 76.9)
    - Before Breakfast, The Stronger, Chamber Music, 1966 Apr (Folder 76.10)
    - The Masque of Queens, 1966 Apr (Folder 76.11)
    - The Beaux Stratagem, 1966 May (Folder 76.12)
    - The Would-be Gentleman, 1966 Oct (Folder 76.13)
    - Cinderella, 1966 Nov (Folder 76.14)
    - Fashion, 1966 Dec (Folder 76.15)
    - Antigone, 1967 Mar (Folder 77.1)
    - Movers and Shakers, 1967 May (Folder 77.2)
    - The Browning Version, 1967 Oct (Folder 77.3)
    - The Island, 1967 Oct (Folder 77.3)
    - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1967 Oct (Folder 77.4)
    - The Pelican, 1967 Nov (Folder 77.5)
    - The Rook This Property is Condemned, The Long Christmas Dinner, 1967 Dec (Folder 77.6)
    - Angelina, The Passionate Pasha, 1968 Feb (Folder 77.7)
    - When We Dead Awaken, 1968 Mar (Folder 77.8)
    - The Women, 1968 Apr (Folder 77.9)
    - The Field God, 1968 May (Folder 77.10)
    - The Odd Lady Shows Her Medals, The Bald Soprano, Passion, Poison and Petrification, 1968 Oct (Folder 78.1)
    - To Travel Blind, 1968 Nov (Folder 78.2)
    - Alcestis, 1968 Dec (Folder 78.3)
    - Honey Sam, Crawling Around, 1969 Dec (Folder 78.4)
    - The Gioconda Smile, 1969 Mar (Folder 78.5)
    - The Bear, The Orchestra, 1969 Apr (Folder 78.6)
    - La Ronde, 1969 May (Folder 78.7)
    - The Good Woman of Setzuan [The Good Person of Szechwan], 1969 Nov (Folder 78.8)
    - Miss Julie, 1969 Dec (Folder 78.9)
    - The Miser, 1970 Feb (Folder 78.10)
    - A Spring Celebration, 1970 Apr (Folder 78.11)
    - Lysistrata, 1970 Oct (Folder 78.12)
    - The Card Game, 1970 Dec (Folder 78.13)
    - The London Merchant, 1971 Mar (Folder 78.14)
    - Camino Real, 1971 May (Folder 78.15)
    - Lady Precious Stream, 1971 Oct (Folder 78.16)
    - The Servant of Two Masters, 1971 Dec (Folder 78.17)
    - You Can’t Take It With You, 1972 Mar (Folder 79.1)
    - Three One Act Plays, Leap Year, Spain, Entrepreneurs of Avenue B, 1972 Apr (Folder 79.2)
    - Street Scene, 1972 Nov (Folder 79.3)
    - The House of Bernanda Alba, 1972 Dec (Folder 79.4)
    - The Country Wife, 1973 Mar (Folder 79.5)
    - Dames at Sea (A Musical), 1973 May (Folder 79.6)
    - Dynamo, 1973 Oct (Folder 79.7)
    - Ah, Wilderness, 1973 Dec (Folder 79.8)
    - Alls Well That Ends Well, 1974 May (Folder 79.9)
    - Six Characters in Search of An Author, 1975 Nov (Folder 79.10)
    - Learned Ladies, 1978 Nov (Folder 79.11)
    - Orpheus Descending, 1979 Oct (Folder 79.12)
    - The Portrait, 1979 Nov (Folder 79.13)
    - The People, Yes, 1972 (Folder 19.30)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1920s (Folder 20.1)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1930s (Folders 20.2-20.3)
    - Miscellaneous — Unidentified, circa 1930-1945 (Folder 5.3)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1940-1959 (Folder 20.4)
    - Miscellaneous - props and make-up, circa 1940-1959 (Folder 20.5)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1950s (Folder 20.6)
    - Miscellaneous – Unidentified, circa 1950s (Folder 24.7 (Oversize))
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1960s (Folder 20.7)
    - Miscellaneous - Unidentified slides, 1970-1971 (Box 83)
    - Candidates for Summer Theatre Program, 1935-1959 (Folder 20.8)
    - Assorted Portraits of Actors, including Eugenie Leontovich and Edgar Barrier, circa 1930s (Folder 20.9)
    - Vassar Experimental Theatre floor plans, undated; (framed) (On shelf)
- Series IV. Drama Department Slides, 1944-1991
  - The Tempest, 1944 Mar (Box 61)
  - Him, 1944 Dec (Box 61)
  - Provok'd Wife, 1949 Mar (Box 61)
  - Gardener's Dog, 1951 Feb (Box 61)
  - Orpheus, 1951 May (Box 61)
  - Much Ado About Nothing, 1955 Mar (Box 61)
  - The Alchemist, 1956 Mar (Box 61)
  - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1956 May (Box 61)
  - The Critic, 1953 Mar (Box 61)
  - Noah, 1957 Mar (Box 61)
  - Him, 1957 May (Box 61)
  - To Damascus, 1958 Mar (Box 61)
  - The Lesson and the Bald Soprano, 1958 Dec (Box 61)
  - The Masque of Camus, 1959 Mar (Box 61)
  - Ring Round the Moon, 1959 May (Box 61)
  - Arms and the Man, 1959 Dec (Box 61)
  - Madwoman of Chaillot, 1960 May (Box 61)
  - Unidentified productions, undated (Box 61)
  - 35 mm slides, production photos, 1964-1991; (approximately 66 boxes) (Box 83)
  - Miscellaneous Slides from Drama Productions, undated (Box 106)
- Series V. Drama Department Audio and Film Reels, 1961-1971
  - 4 audio reels from The Voice of Vassar, 1961; (4 audio reels) (Box 83)
  - 2 audio reels from Movers and Shakers, 1966; (2 audio reels) (Box 83)
  - Unidentified production, probably Camino Real or One Third of a Nation, 1970-1971; (1 film reel, super 8) (Box 83)
  - Vintage slide projector, undated (Box 83)
  - Instructional footage, undated; (35mm film, 3 rolls) (Box 83)
- Series VI. Drama Department Production Material, circa 1910-2021
  - Production Files, circa 1910-2019
    - Production files, in chronological order, circa 1910-1931 (Box 26)
    - Pageant of Athena - Photographs, 1915 (Box 95)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1915-1947 (Box 59)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1931-1934 (Box 27)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1934-1937 (Box 28)
    - Tonight We Improvise (Experimental Theatre), 1937-1938 (Box 95)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1937-1940 (Box 29)
    - Vassar's Folly, 1938, 1940 (Box 44)
    - Orpheus (Experimental Theatre), 1939 (Box 95)
    - Escape or No Escape (Experimental Theatre), 1940 (Box 95)
    - Our Town (Experimental Theatre), 1940 (Box 95)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1940-1941 (Box 30)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1941-1944 (Box 31)
    - Phoenix (Experimental Theatre), 1942 (Box 95)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1944-1948 (Box 32)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1947-1962 (Box 60)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1948-1952 (Box 33)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1952-1954 (Box 34)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1954-1955 (Box 35)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1956-1957 (Box 36)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1957-1958 (Box 37)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1958-1960 (Box 38)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1960-1962 (Box 39)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1962-1972 (Box 62)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1962-1963 (Box 40)
    - Hansel and Gretel, 1963 (Box 44)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1963-1964 (Box 41)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1965-1966 (Box 42)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1967-1970 (Box 43)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1971-1973 (Box 49)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1972-1979 (Box 63)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1973-1974 (Box 50)
    - Production files, in chronological order, 1975-1979 (Box 51)
    - The Tempest, 1980 Feb 21-23 (Box 52)
    - Right You Are, 1980 Feb 28 - Mar 1 (Box 52)
    - First Breeze of Summer, 1980 Mar 27-29 (Box 52)
    - The Knight of the Burning Pestle, 1980 Apr 18, 20 (Box 52)
    - The History of the American Film, 1980 Apr 24-26 (Box 52)
    - The House of Mirth, 1980 Oct 9-11; (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - Fuente Ovejuna, 1980 Nov 20-23 (Box 52)
    - Dear Antoine, 1980 Dec 5-6 (Box 52)
    - Bury the Dead, 1980 Oct 30 - Nov 1 (Box 52)
    - Once in a Lifetime, 1981 Feb 26-28; (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - The Dance of Death, 1981 Mar 27-28; (3 folders) (Box 52)
    - To Be Young, Gifted and Black, 1981 Apr 24-25 (Box 52)
    - Fumed Oak / Woyzeck, 1981 May 1-2 (Box 52)
    - Uncommon Women and Others, 1981 Oct 1-3 (Box 52)
    - Europeans by Henry James, 1981 Oct 8-10 (Box 52)
    - Cymbeline, 1981 Nov 18-21; (3 folders) (Box 53)
    - Look Homeward, Angel, 1981 Dec 4-5; (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Video Life, 1982 Feb 19-20 (Box 53)
    - War and Peace, 1982 Feb 24-27; (3 folders) (Box 53)
    - The Rose Tattoo, 1982 Apr 22-24 (Box 53)
    - Undine [Ondine], 1982 Apr 30 - May 1 (Box 53)
    - Stage Door, 1982 Sep 30 - Oct 2 (Box 53)
    - Scapino, 1982 Oct 7-9 (Box 53)
    - Love for Love, 1982 Nov 18-20 (Box 53)
    - Aspern Papers, 1982 Dec 3-4 (Box 53)
    - Between Two Thieves, 1983 Feb 25-26 (Box 53)
    - The Seagull, 1983 Mar 31 - Apr 2; (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Dynamo, 1983 Apr 22-23 (Box 53)
    - The Further Adventures of Sally, 1983 May 6-8 (Box 53)
    - The Shoemaker's Prodigious Wife, 1983 Apr 28-30 (Box 53)
    - House of Blue Leaves, 1983 Sep 29 - Oct 1 (Box 53)
    - The Heiress, 1983 Oct 21-22 (Box 53)
    - Hedda Gabler, 1983 Oct 6-8 (Box 53)
    - The Lady's Not for Burning, 1983 Nov 17-19 (Box 54)
    - The Ponder Heart, 1983 Dec 1-3 (Box 54)
    - When We Are Married, 1984 Feb 23-25 (Box 54)
    - J. B., 1984 Mar 2-3 (Box 54)
    - Bus Stop, 1984 Apr 6-7 (Box 54)
    - The Children's Hour, 1984 Apr 19-21 (Box 54)
    - Life is a Dream, 1984 Apr 20-21 (Box 54)
    - Morning's at Seven, 1984 Oct 18-20 (Box 54)
    - A Clearing in the Woods, 1984 Oct 26-27 (Box 54)
    - Hitchin' in the Company of Saints, 1984 Oct 28, Nov 4 (Box 54)
    - Ladies in Retirement, 1984 Nov 29-Dec 1 (Box 54)
    - The Crucible, 1984 Dec 7-8 (Box 54)
    - Hippolytus, 1985 Feb 28-Mar 2 (Box 54)
    - The Affairs of Anatol, 1985 Mar 1-2 (Box 54)
    - Hay Fever, 1985 Apr 26-27 (Box 54)
    - You Can’t Take It With You, 1985 May 2-4 (Box 54)
    - A Peculiar Position / Table No. 7, 1985 Oct 4-5 (Box 54)
    - The Matchmaker, 1985 Oct 10-12 (Box 54)
    - Vieux Carre, 1985 Nov 22-23 (Box 55)
    - Women Beware Women, 1985 Dec 5-7 (Box 55)
    - Under Milkwood, 1986 Feb 21-22 (Box 55)
    - Dogg's Hamlet, Cahoot's Macbeth, 1986 Feb 27-Mar 1 (Box 55)
    - Arms and the Man, 1986 Apr 26-27 (Box 55)
    - Dark at the Top of the Stairs, 1986 May 1-3 (Box 55)
    - The Lesson / The Maids, 1986 Oct 3-4 (Box 55)
    - Merrily We Roll Along, 1986 Oct 9-11 (Box 55)
    - The Age of Innocence, 1986 Nov 18-22 (Box 55)
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1986 Dec 4-6 (Box 55)
    - Antigone, 1987 Feb 27-28 (Box 55)
    - Nothing but the Truth, 1987 Mar 5-7 (Box 55)
    - Private Life of the Master Race, 1987 May 1-2 (Box 55)
    - Another Part of the Forest, 1987 May 7-9 (Box 55)
    - Liberty Belles, 1987 Oct 1-3 (Box 55)
    - The Visit, 1987 Oct 8-10 (Box 55)
    - The Portrait, 1987 Nov 15-17 (Box 55)
    - Morn to Midnight, 1987 Nov 18-21 (Box 55)
    - Morn to Midnight, 1987 Nov 18-21 (Box 56)
    - Pack of Lies, 1987 Dec 3-5 (Box 56)
    - Picnic, 1988 Feb 18-20 (Box 56)
    - The House of Bernanda Alba, 1988 Apr 22-23 (Box 56)
    - Tonight at 8:30, 1988 Apr 28 (Box 56)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1988 Sep 29 - Oct 1 (Box 56)
    - Summer and Smoke, 1988 Oct 6-8 (Box 56)
    - The Trojan Women, 1988 Nov 17-19 (Box 56)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1988 Feb 25-27 (Box 56)
    - The Schoolmistress, 1988 Dec 7-10; (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - The Prime of Miss Jean Brodie, 1989 Feb 24-25 (Box 56)
    - The Good Person of Szechwan, 1989 Mar 2-4 (Box 56)
    - Three Plays by Yeats, Riddled with Light, 1989 Apr 26-29 (Box 56)
    - The Three Sisters, 1989 May 4-6 (Box 56)
    - Six characters in Search of An Author, 1989 Oct 5-7; (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - Six characters in Search of An Author, 1989 Oct 5-7; (VHS and CD) (Box 57)
    - Fen, 1989 Oct 26-28 (Box 57)
    - The Man Who Came to Dinner, 1989 Dec 7-9 (Box 57)
    - Praying Mantis, 1990 Feb 22-24 (Box 57)
    - Toys in the Attic, 1990 Mar 1-3 (Box 57)
    - Blithe Spirit, 1990 Apr 26-28 (Box 57)
    - Tango, 1990 Dec 6-8 (Box 57)
    - The Rivals, 1990 May 3-5 (Box 57)
    - Machinal, 1990 Oct 4-6 (Box 57)
    - Tartuffe, 1990 Oct 11-13 (Box 57)
    - Twelfth Night, 1990 Nov 29 - Dec 1 (Box 57)
    - The Glass Menagerie, 1991 Feb 21 - 24 (Box 57)
    - Man and Superman, 1991 Feb 27 - Mar 1 (Box 57)
    - The Eumenides, 1991 Apr 25 - 27; (2 folders) (Box 57)
    - The Heiress, 1991 May 2 - 4 (Box 58)
    - The Wheel, 1991 Oct 3 - 6, 10 - 12 (Box 58)
    - The Winters Tale, 1991 Oct 11 - 13 (Box 58)
    - Crimes of the Heart, 1991 Nov 21 - 23 (Box 58)
    - A Christmas Carol, 1991 Dec 5 - 8 (Box 58)
    - Happy Birthday Vincent, 1992 Feb 20 - 23; (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Spring Awakening, 1992 Feb 27 - Mar 1 (Box 58)
    - Spring Awakening, 1992 Feb 27 - Mar 1 (Box 58)
    - Fefu & Her Friends, 1992 Apr 8 - 12 (Box 58)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1992 Apr 23 - 26 (Box 58)
    - A Sampler of the 20th Century: Three Short Plays, 1992 Oct 8 - 11 (Box 58)
    - Euripides’ The Bacchae, 1992 Nov 5 - 7 (Box 58)
    - A Mouthful of Birds, 1992 Nov 18 - 22 (Box 58)
    - After the Fact, 1992 (Box 58)
    - Female Parts, 1993 Feb 25 - 28 (Box 58)
    - Macbeth, 1993 Apr 1 - 4; (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Dream Times, 1993 Apr 8 - 10 (Box 58)
    - The Reign of Wazobia, 1993 Apr 14 (Box 58)
    - The Government Inspector, 1993 Apr 22 - 25 (Box 58)
    - The Threshold Above, 1993 May 1 - 2 (Box 58)
    - Uncle Vanya, 1993 Oct 7 - 10 (Box 58)